<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resource>   ShipView your ship and its equipment in the currently selected Hangar.P.E.T.View your P.E.T. and its equipment in the currently selected Hangar.DronesView your Drones and their equipment in the currently selected HangarSwitch to configuration 1Switch to configuration 2   Are you sure you want to downgrade? Your equipped items are better.   LasersRocket LaunchersExtrasGenerators   GearsAI Protocols   StatisticsNew ShipsClose New ShipsWarp InActivateAllocateRename   InventoryFilterShow All   AmmunitionWeaponsGeneratorsExtrasP.E.T. GearsP.E.T. ProtocolsCBSDronesRaw MaterialsSpecialP.E.T.BoostersShips &amp; DesignsHardware   NameTypeLevelDescriptionQuantityCapacityAbsorptionCooldownDurabilityDamageDamage BonusShield StealInstalled onRange   SellQuick BuyRepairUpgradeConfigure   Level: %NUMBER%Upgrade Level: %NUMBER%Damage: %NUMBER%%   OKCancelName is too long.Name is too short.Contains characters that are not allowed.   Add hangarPurchase an additional Hangar.A Hangar lets you store ships and quickly switch between them by activating or warping a different Hangar. Do you want to buy a Hangar for %hangar_price%?It seems that the price of this item has changed. Do you still want to buy a Hangar for %hangar_price%?A Hangar lets you store ships and quickly switch between them by activating or warping a different Hangar. Unfortunately, you do not have the full %hangar_price% required to buy one.BuyHangar successfully purchased.   Allocate shipUse the allocate button to allocate this ship to the currently selected Hangar.Allocate a new ship to the currently selected Hangar. Warning! Any ship currently occupying that Hangar will be automatically sold!Allocate   Clear ConfigurationDeletes current configuration.Warning! You are about to delete your ship´s current configuration. Do you really wish to proceed ?Delete   Rename HangarRename your Hangar as you please. (This feature is only available with an active Premium subscription.)   Rename P.E.T.You can rename your P.E.T. for %pet_rename_price%.   UpgradeUpgrade to level %level%!Chance of success:Total costs:UpgradeFAILUREUpgrade attempt failed.SUCCESSUpgraded to level %level%!Upgrade damage bonus to %amount%%.Upgrade shield bonus to %amount%%.Upgrade durability bonus to %amount%.Upgrade booster bonus to %amount%.Upgrade repair bonus to %amount%.Upgrade deflector shield bonus minutes to %amount%.Upgraded damage bonus to %amount%%.Upgraded shield bonus to %amount%%.Upgraded durability bonus to %amount%.Upgraded booster bonus to %amount%.Upgraded repair bonus to %amount%.Upgraded deflector shield bonus minutes to %amount%.   RepairRepair this drone for %price% %currency%?Its level will drop from Level %level.from% to Level %level.to%.Repair your ship for %price% %currency%, and prepare for the next round!Repair the selected item for %price% %currency%?Repair   Configure   SellHow many do you want to sell?Are you sure that you want to sell this item for %price% %currency%?AmountSell forMax.Sell   Activate HangarSwitch to the ship and its current position in the selected Hangar for %shipwarp_price%.Ship WarpWarp the ship in the selected Hangar to your current position and switch to it for %shipwarp_price%.This hangar activation is free, because you are at the Company station.   Buy a P.E.T. slotDo you really want to buy a P.E.T. slot for %buy_price%?Buy   You don't have a P.E.T.You don't have any drones.HullNanohullLaser-DamageSpeedShield CapacityShield Hull DistributionNameFuelLevelP.E.T. XPHealthLaser DamageShield CapacityShield Hull DistributionLevelReceived DamageDamage / Shield BonusDrone XPXP for next level   Activating new ship   ErrorERROR !!!\nThe requested ship could not be found.ERROR !!!\nThe requested hangar could not be found.ERROR !!!\nYou don't have a P.E.T.ERROR !!!\nThis price is incorrect.ERROR !!!\nYou have insufficient funds.ERROR !!!\nThat's the wrong slot.ERROR !!!\nThe requested drone could not be found.ERROR !!!\nShip or configuration not found.ERROR !!!\nYou have too many hangars.ERROR !!!\nYou do not have a Premium account.ERROR !!!\nThat is an invalid name.ERROR !!!\nThe requested design could not be found.ERROR !!!\nSome items could not be equipped.ERROR !!!\nThis target can't be activated.<item name="equipment_popup.error.title"><![CDATA[Error]]></item>
    <item name="NO_SUCH_SHIP"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nThe requested ship could not be found.]]></item>
    <item name="NO_SUCH_HANGAR"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nThe requested hangar could not be found.]]></item>
    <item name="USER_HAS_NO_PET"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nYou don't have a P.E.T.]]></item>
    <item name="INCORRECT_PRICE"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nThis price is incorrect.]]></item>
    <item name="NOT_ENOUGH_MONEY"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nYou have insufficient funds.]]></item>
    <item name="INCORRECT_SLOT_INDEX"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nThat's the wrong slot.]]></item>
    <item name="NO_SUCH_DRONE"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nThe requested drone could not be found.]]></item>
    <item name="WRONG_SHIP_ID_OR_CONFIG"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nShip or configuration not found.]]></item>
    <item name="TOO_MANY_HANGARS"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nYou have too many hangars.]]></item>
    <item name="NOT_PREMIUM_USER"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nYou do not have a Premium account.]]></item>
    <item name="INVALID_NAME"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nThat is an invalid name.]]></item>
    <item name="NO_SUCH_DESIGN"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nThe requested design could not be found.]]></item>
    <item name="SOME_ITEMS_WERE_NOT_EQUIPPED"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nSome items could not be equipped.]]></item>
    <item name="ILLEGAL_TARGET_SHIPACTIVATION"><![CDATA[ERROR !!!\nThis target can't be activated.]]></item>
</resource>
